speedmonkey.net 2008-06-08

# SpeedMonkey Privacy Policy -SpeedMonkey Privacy Policy- Pop culture Celebrity News, Gossip, Reviews & Advice Speedmonkey.net

#### Details

Views: 2,096

Rating: 3

Votes: 0

Comments: 

#### Rate

  *   *   *   *   *   * 

#### Images

#### Tags

 | 

## Disclaimer  

SpeedMonkey.net is all about gossip and satire. The content that is published contains rumors, speculation, assumptions, opinions, and factual information. Postings may contain erroneous or inaccurate information. The owner of this site does not insure the accurateness of any content presented on SpeedMonkey.net.

## Personal Information that SpeedMonkey May Collect Online:

SpeedMonkey collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers. SpeedMonkey may also collect business information from sole proprietorships some of which could constitute personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity. 

SpeedMonkey does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our sites are structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. 

How SpeedMonkey Uses Personal Information Collected Online 

Unless you consent, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, provide operational notices and in program record-keeping. 

At any time you can add or remove your name from a SpeedMonkey list by contacting us at monkey@speedmonkey.net 

SpeedMonkey may also release personal information to appropriate governmental authorities under the following circumstances: 

\- Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by a government agency conducting investigations or proceedings; 

\- Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of; 

\- Where warranted by a company's failure to participate in the advertising self-regulatory process or respond to an online privacy complaint, or where a company fails to honor the recommendations of the National Advertising Division, Children's Advertising Review Unit, National Advertising Review Board or; 

\- Where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

## Images  

We receive images from several contributors and we have several writers. We always strive to use only open source, royalty free images or else we pay the appropriate fee to use images through a service.

Occasionally, we get images that are believed to be royalty free only to find out that they are owned by another party. When we are notified, we make these images unavailable to users. If the images in question are proven to be owned by a third party then we delete the images from our servers.    

If you believe you are the owner of any images you see on this site, please send us an email and we will remove them.  

Read more gossip
